Guide to the Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees: 1915-1985
Brotherhood of Railway, Airline, and Steamship Clerks, Freight Handlers, Express, and Station Employees
- Series XXI. ORGANIZATION
  - Sub-Series 230-71. Organization
    - Florida East Coast, 1922-1932 (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 230-72. Organization
    - International & Great Northern (I. & G. N.), 1941-1945 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 230-73. Organization
    - Des Moines Union, 1921-1953 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 230-74. Organization
    - Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway, 1944-1955 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway, 1941-1943 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Oregon Short Line, 1922-1934 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 230-75. Organization
    - Union Railway Company of Memphis, 1945 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 230-76. Organization
    - Chicago Great Western, 1941-1953 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 230-78. Organization
    - Colorado & Southern, 1946-1953 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 230-79. Organization
    - Kentucky & Indiana Terminal Railroad Company, 1935-1949 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 230-82. Organization
    - Florida East Coast, 1939-1956 (Box 94, Folder 20)
    - Florida East Coast, 1933-1938 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 230-84. Organization
    - Missouri Pacific, 1945-1947 (Box 95, Folder 2)
      Nov. 1945-Aug. 1947.
    - Missouri Pacific, 1945 (Box 95, Folder 3)
      July 1945-Oct. 1945.
    - Missouri Pacific, 1944-1945 (Box 95, Folder 4)
      April 1944-June 1945.
  - Sub-Series 230-85. Organization
    - Ann Arbor, 1935-1949 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 230-86. Organization
    - Trunk Line Freight Inspection Bureau, Trunk Association, 1938-1946 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 230-87. Organization
    - Fort Wayne and Denver City (Ft. W. & D. C.) Colorado and Southern, 1935-1953 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 230-88. Organization
    - Boston and Albany Railroad, 1923-1930 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Indianapolis Union Railway Company, 1936-1946 (Box 95, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 230-89. Organization
    - Los Angeles & Salt Lake Railroad, 1925-1948 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 230-90. Organization
    - Minneapolis, St. Paul & Sault Ste. Marie (M. St. P. & S. S. M.)-Soo Line, 1935-1940 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - Minneapolis, St. Paul & Sault Ste. Marie (M. St. P. & S. S. M.)-Soo Line, 1923-1930 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Western Weighing & Inspection Bureau, 1946-1956 (Box 96, Folder 2)
      Aug. 1946-1956.
    - Western Weighing & Inspection Bureau, 1946 (Box 96, Folder 3)
      March 12, 1946-July 1946.
    - Western Weighing & Inspection Bureau, 1945-1946 (Box 96, Folder 4)
      Oct. 1945-March 11, 1946.
    - Western Weighing & Inspection Bureau, 1940-1946 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Western Weighing & Inspection Bureau, 1940-1946 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Western Weighing & Inspection Bureau, 1945-1946 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Western Weighing & Inspection Bureau, 1945-1946 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - Western Weighing & Inspection Bureau, 1940-1946 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - Western Weighing & Inspection Bureau, 1945-1946 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Western Weighing & Inspection Bureau, 1945-1947 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - Western Weighing & Inspection Bureau, 1943-1945 (Box 96, Folder 12)
      1943-Sept. 1945.
  - Sub-Series 230-91. Organization
    - Western Maryland, 1940-1945 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 230-92. Organization
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford (N. Y. N. H. & H.), 1942-1944 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford (N. Y. N. H. & H.), 1941 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford (N. Y. N. H. & H.), 1932-1940 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford, 1923-1931 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 230-93. Organization
    - Midland Valley-Kansas, Oklahoma and Gulf Railroad, 1923-1941 (Box 98, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 230-94. Organization
    - Central Freight Association, 1935-1949 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 230-95. Organization
    - Peoria & Pekin Union Railway, 1934-1946 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 230-96. Organization
    - Chesapeake and Ohio (C. & O.), 1941-1944 (Box 87, Folder 9)
      1941-Feb. 29, 1944.
    - Chesapeake and Ohio (C. & O.), 1936-1940 (Box 87, Folder 10)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio (C. & O.), 1935 (Box 87, Folder 11)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad (C. & O. R. R.) (2), 1934 (Box 88, Folder 1)
      Aug. 21, 1934-Oct 9, 1934.
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad (C. & O. R. R.) (3), 1934 (Box 88, Folder 2)
      Oct. 10, 1934-Dec. 31, 1934.
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad (C. & O. R. R.) (1), 1934 (Box 88, Folder 3)
      Jan. 5, 1934-Aug. 20, 1934.
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad, 1933 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Chesapeake and Ohio Railroad, 1926-1932 (Box 88, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 230-97. Organization
    - Norfolk & Western Railway, 1953-1954 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Norfolk & Western Railway, 1946-1952 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Norfolk & Western Railway, 1944-1945 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Norfolk & Western Railway, 1942-1943 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 230-98. Organization
    - Chicago & Eastern Illinois Railway, 1941-1953 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 230-99. Organization
    - Boston & Maine, 1944-1952 (Box 98, Folder 5)
      June 1944-52.
    - Boston & Maine, 1941-1944 (Box 98, Folder 6)
      1941-May 1944.
  - Sub-Series 230-100. Organization
    - Gulf, Mobile, and Ohio Railroad, 1944-1953 (Box 98, Folder 9)
      March 1944-53.
    - 230-100(a). Gulf, Mobile, and Ohio Railroad, 1935-1944 (Box 98, Folder 10)
      1935-February 1944.
    - 230-100(b). Gulf, Mobile, and Northern, 1920-1941 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 230-104. Organization
    - New York Central Lines West, 1942-1944 (Box 90, Folder 10)
      1942-Feb. 24, 1944.
    - New York Central-Lines West, 1940-1941 (Box 90, Folder 11)
    - New York Central-Lines East, 1941 (Box 90, Folder 14)
    - New York Central Lines (N.Y.C. Lines), 1934-1938 (Box 90, Folder 15)
    - New York Central Lines, 1924-1932 (Box 90, Folder 16)
    - Central Railroad of New Jersey, 1941-1956 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 230-106. Organization
    - Chicago & Eastern Illinois Railway (C. & E. I.), 1933-1940 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Chicago & Eastern Illinois Railway, 1924-1931 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Denver Union Terminal Company, 1953-1954 (Box 98, Folder 17)
      June 1953-June 1954.
  - Sub-Series 230-107. Organization
    - Missouri Pacific, 1942-1944 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      Nov. 24, 1942-March 31, 1944.
    - Missouri Pacific, 1942 (Box 95, Folder 6)
      1942-Nov. 16, 1942.
    - Missouri Pacific, 1941 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Missouri Pacific, 1934-1940 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Missouri Pacific, 1924-1933 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Houston Belt & Terminal Railway, 1946-1953 (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 230-108. Organization
    - Chicago & Western Indiana, 1921-1953 (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 230-110. Organization
    - Midland Valley Railroad, 1941-1953 (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 230-111. Organization
    - Maine Central Portland Terminal, 1934-1953 (Box 98, Folder 22)
    - Maine Central, 1931 (Box 98, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 230-112. Organization
    - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago & St. Louis (C. C. C. & St. L.), 1944-1953 (Box 98, Folder 24)
      June 1944-53.
    - Cleveland, Cincinnati, Chicago & St. Louis (C. C. C. & St. L.), 1943-1944 (Box 98, Folder 25)
      1943-May 1944.
  - Sub-Series 230-113. Organization
    - New York, Chicago & St. Louis (N. Y. C. & St. L.)-Nickel Plate, 1943-1953 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 230-115. Organization
    - Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad (C. B. & Q.), 1941-1943 (Box 93, Folder 11)
      1941-Dec. 31, 1943.
    - Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad (C. B. & Q.), 1933-1940 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Chicago, Burlington and Quincy Railroad, 1924-1932 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 230-117. Organization
    - Baltimore & Ohio, 1934-1938 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Baltimore & Ohio, 1924-1931 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Baltimore & Ohio, 1942-1943 (Box 89, Folder 5)
      1942-Dec. 31, 1943.
    - Baltimore & Ohio R. R., 1941 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Baltimore & Ohio R. R., 1939-1940 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis (T. R. R. A. of St. L.), 1941-1945 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 230-118. Organization
    - New York, New Haven, and Hartford (N. Y. N. H. & H.), 1944-1956 (Box 99, Folder 7)
      March 1944-56.
  - Sub-Series 230-120. Organization
    - Chicago and Alton, 1924-1929 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 230-122. Organization
    - Ann Arbor Railroad, 1924-1931 (Box 95, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 230-126. Organization
    - Great Northern, 1925-1932 (Box 85, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 230-127. Organization
    - Chicago and North Western (C. & N. W.), 1933-1940 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Chicago and North Western Railway, 1925-1932 (Box 92, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 230-129. Organization
    - Kansas City, Mexico and Orient, 1925-1928 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 230-132. Organization
    - Kansas City Southern Railway System (K. C. S.), 1939-1940 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Kansas City Southern, 1930-1938 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - Kansas City Southern, 1925-1928 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 230-138. Organization
    - Chicago, Indianapolis and Louisville, 1925-1934 (Box 90, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 230-139. Organization
    - Central of Georgia, 1937-1940 (Box 79a, Folder 3)
    - Central of Georgia, 1933-1936 (Box 79a, Folder 4)
    - Central of Georgia, 1925-1936 (Box 79a, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 230-140. Organization
    - Chicago Great Western, 1935-1940 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Chicago Great Western, 1925-1929 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 230-147. Organization
    - International & Great Northern (I. & G. N.)-Gulf Coast Lines, 1925-1938 (Box 94, Folder 3)
      1925 and 1934-38.
  - Sub-Series 230-148. Organization
    - Chicago, Rock Island and Pacific Railway, 1925-1940 (Box 94, Folder 7)
      1925 and 1936-1940.
  - Sub-Series 230-171. Organization
    - Minneapolis and St. Louis, 1929 (Box 91, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 230-177. Organization
    - Colorado & Southern, 1928-1929 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 230-179. Organization
    - Terminal Railroad Association of St. Louis (T. R. R. A. of St. L.), 1928-1940 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 230-180. Organization
    - Texas & Pacific Railway, 1928-1932 (Box 85, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 230-182. Organization
    - Louisiana & Arkansas Railway, 1928-1930 (Box 78, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 230-185. Organization
    - Kentucky and Indiana Terminal, 1929-1933 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 230-187. Organization
    - Western Pacific, 1929-1930 (Box 88, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 230-190. Organization
    - Duluth, South Shore and Atlantic, 1929-1931 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 230-198. Organization
    - Hocking Valley, 1929-1938 (Box 91, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 230-202. Organization
    - Peoria & Pekin Union Railway, 1929-1930 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 230-208. Organization
    - Toledo Terminal Railroad, 1930 (Box 91, Folder 17)
      1930 May 17
  - Sub-Series 230-209. Organization
    - Norfolk & Western Railway, 1941 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Norfolk & Western Railway, 1940 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Norfolk & Western Railway, 1939 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Norfolk & Western Railway, 1938 (Box 97, Folder 16)
      Aug. 25, 1938-Dec. 1938.
    - Norfolk & Western Railway, 1938 (Box 97, Folder 17)
      Jan.1938-Aug. 17, 1938.
    - Norfolk & Western Railway, 1933-1937 (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - Norfolk & Western Railway, 1930 (Box 97, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 230-213. Organization
    - Western Weighing & Inspection Bureau, 1940-1942 (Box 96, Folder 13)
      July 1940-1942.
    - Western Weighing & Inspection Bureau, 1940 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Western Weighing & Inspection Bureau, 1933-1939 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Western Weighing & Inspection Bureau, 1931 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 230-216. Organization
    - Rutland Railroad, 1932 (Box 97, Folder 8)
      1932 July
  - Sub-Series 230-220. Organization
    - Railroad Perishable Inspection Agency, 1936-1940 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 230-222. Organization
    - Georgia Railroad and Western Railway of Alabama, 1933 (Box 99, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 230-224. Organization
    - Freight Forwarding Company Employees, 1935-1940 (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - Freight Forwarding Company Employees, 1934 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Freight Forwarding Company Employees, Toledo, 1935 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 230-229. Organization
    - Kansas City Terminal Company, 1933-1940 (Box 90, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 230-238. Organization
    - Sioux City Terminal Railway Company, 1933-1943 (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 230-239. Organization
    - Fruit Growers Express, 1933-1941 (Box 100, Folder 6)
  - Sub-Series 230-244. Organization
    - Washington Terminal, 1933-1940 (Box 92, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 230-249. Organization
    - Atlanta Joint Terminals, 1937-1935 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 230-271. Organization
    - Lake Superior Terminal & Transfer Railway Company, 1934-1938 (Box 101, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 230-288. Organization
    - Chicago North Shore & Milwaukee Railway, 1935 (Box 99, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 230-292. Organization
    - The Belt Railway of Chicago, 1935 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 230-309. Organization
    - Meridian Terminal Company, 1943-1946 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 230-311. Organization
    - Motor Carriers, 1951 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 230-312. Organization
    - Merchants Shippers Association, 1938-1951 (Box 99, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 230-313. Organization
    - Rock Island-Frisco Terminal Company, 1938-1944 (Box 99, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 230-316. Organization
    - Chicago Stock Yards District Agency, 1946 (Box 99, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 230-319. Organization
    - Chattanooga Station Company, 1945-1953 (Box 99, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 230-322. Organization
    - Western Warehouse, 1939-1943 (Box 99, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 230-323. Organization
    - Lackawanna & Wyoming Valley, 1937-1943 (Box 99, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 230-325. Organization
    - Texas Electric Railway, 1933-1945 (Box 99, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 230-326. Organization
    - New York, Susquehanna & Western Railroad, 1943-1948 (Box 99, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 230-329. Organization
    - Union Motor Coach Terminal Company, Chicago, 1940-1953 (Box 99, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 230-332. Organization
    - National Harbours Board, Montreal, 1947-1948 (Box 99, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 230-333. Organization
    - 230-333(b). Western Railway of Alabama, 1935-1946 (Box 99, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 230-334. Organization
    - Spokane International Railway, 1935-1945 (Box 99, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 230-335. Organization
    - New Orleans & Lower Coast, 1947-1957 (Box 99, Folder 32)
  - Sub-Series 230-336. Organization
    - Detroit & Cleveland Navigation Company, 1922-1946 (Box 99, Folder 33)
  - Sub-Series 230-337. Organization
    - Salt Lake Terminal, 1938-1947 (Box 99, Folder 34)
  - Sub-Series 230-338. Organization
    - National Trailways Bus Depot, 1941-1951 (Box 99, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 230-339. Organization
    - Fort Dodge, Des Moines and Southern (Ft. D. D. M. & S.), 1935-1944 (Box 99, Folder 36)
  - Sub-Series 230-340. Organization
    - Augusta Union Station Company, 1941-1957 (Box 100, Folder 1)
  - Sub-Series 230-341. Organization
    - Parmalee Transportation Company, 1946 (Box 100, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 230-343. Organization
    - Ashley, Drew & Northern Railway Company, 1941-1945 (Box 100, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 230-344. Organization
    - Fruit Growers Express Company, 1943-1945 (Box 100, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 230-345. Organization
    - Fonda, Johnstown & Gloversville Railroad (Box 100, Folder 7)
  - Sub-Series 230-346. Organization
    - Norfolk & Portsmouth Belt Line Railroad, 1939-1956 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 230-347. Organization
    - Norfolk Terminal Railway, 1941-1956 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 230-350. Organization
    - Lake Terminal Railroad, 1938-1952 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 230-351. Organization
    - Georgia and Florida, 1938-1955 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 230-352. Organization
    - Lehigh & Hudson River, 1921-1952 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 230-354. Organization
    - Spokane Union Station, 1948 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 230-355. Organization
    - Toronto Terminal Railways, 1938-1943 (Box 99, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 230-355. Organization
    - East Portland Freight Terminal, 1946 (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 230-356. Organization
    - Cleveland Union Terminal, 1946-1951 (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 230-359. Organization
    - Baltimore & Ohio, Chicago Terminal, 1946-1951 (Box 100, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 230-363. Organization
    - Hannibal Union Station, 1930-1937 (Box 100, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 230-365. Organization
    - Pittsburgh, Chartiers & Youghiogheny Railway, 1941-1945 (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 230-366. Organization
    - Akron Union Passenger Depot Company, 1942-1944 (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 230-367. Organization
    - Santa Fe Tie & Lumber Preserving Company (Somerville, Texas), 1944-1951 (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - Santa Fe Tie & Lumber Preserving Company (Somerville, Texas), Lodge No. 1096, 1942-1944 (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 230-369. Organization
    - Ogden Union Stockyards, 1942-1946 (Box 100, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 230-371. Organization
    - Parmalee Transportation Company, 1939-1941 (Box 100, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 230-372. Organization
    - Missouri-Illinois Railroad, 1930-1944 (Box 100, Folder 25)
  - Sub-Series 230-374. Organization
    - Fred Harvey Service, Inc., 1946-1950 (Box 100, Folder 26)
  - Sub-Series 230-375. Organization
    - New York Central Building Corporation, 1953-1954 (Box 100, Folder 27)
  - Sub-Series 230-379. Organization
    - Goldsboro Union Station Company, 1942-1944 (Box 100, Folder 29)
  - Sub-Series 230-380. Organization
    - Santa Fe Trail Transportation Company, 1942-1943 (Box 100, Folder 30)
  - Sub-Series 230-381. Organization
    - Detroit & Mackinac Railway, 1937-1946 (Box 100, Folder 31)
  - Sub-Series 230-383. Organization
    - 230-383(a). Air Transport Industry, 1940-1943 (Box 100, Folder 32)
    - 230-383(b). Air Transport Industry, Pan American Airways System, 1943-1944 (Box 100, Folder 33)
      1943-Sept. 1944.
  - Sub-Series 230-385. Organization
    - Southeastern Demurrage & Storage Bureau Southern Weighing & Inspection Bureau, 1928-1953 (Box 100, Folder 35)
  - Sub-Series 230-387. Organization
    - American Refrigerator Transit Company, 1944-1948 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - American Refrigerator Transit Company, 1934-1943 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - Sub-Series 230-388. Organization
    - Burlington Refrigerator Express Company, 1936-1946 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 230-389. Organization
    - South Buffalo Railway Company, 1940-1945 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 230-390. Organization
    - Philadelphia, Bethlehem & New England Railroad, 1940-1944 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - Sub-Series 230-393. Organization
    - Texas City Terminal Railway Company, 1943-1953 (Box 101, Folder 8)
  - Sub-Series 230-394. Organization
    - Savannah & Atlanta Railway, 1938-1949 (Box 101, Folder 9)
  - Sub-Series 230-395. Organization
    - Chicago Railroad Freight Collection Association, 1937-1943 (Box 101, Folder 10)
  - Sub-Series 230-396. Organization
    - Wichita Union Terminal Railway Company (The Wichita Terminal Association), 1934-1944 (Box 101, Folder 11)
  - Sub-Series 230-397. Organization
    - Lake Superior Terminal & Transfer Railway, 1943-1953 (Box 101, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 230-398. Organization
    - Southern Freight Tariff Bureau-Atlanta, Georgia, 1941-1954 (Box 101, Folder 14)
  - Sub-Series 230-399. Organization
    - Joint Stockyards Agency-East St. Louis, Illinois, 1943-1944 (Box 101, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 230-400. Organization
    - New England Transportation Company-New York, New Haven & Hartford Railroad (N. Y. N. H. & H.), 1943-1949 (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - Manistee & Northeastern Railway Company, 1938-1943 (Box 101, Folder 17)
  - Sub-Series 230-405. Organization
    - Union Passenger Depot of Galveston, 1944-1955 (Box 101, Folder 18)
  - Sub-Series 230-406. Organization
    - Winston-Salem Southbound Railroad, 1941 (Box 101, Folder 23)
  - Sub-Series 230-407. Organization
    - McKeesport Connecting Railroad, 1942-1952 (Box 101, Folder 19)
  - Sub-Series 230-408. Organization
    - Patapsco & Back Rivers Railroad, 1944-1954 (Box 101, Folder 20)
  - Sub-Series 230-410. Organization
    - Chicago, Aurora & Elgin, 1938-1950 (Box 101, Folder 21)
  - Sub-Series 230-411. Organization
    - Macon Terminal Company, 1941-1942 (Box 100, Folder 34)
    - Tremont & Gulf Railway Company, 1943-1944 (Box 101, Folder 22)
  - Sub-Series 230-413. Organization
    - Trailways Bus Depot-St. Louis, 1944-1949 (Box 101, Folder 24)
  - Sub-Series 230-416. Organization
    - Pan American Airways Inc., 1952 (Box 101, Folder 25)
      July 19, 1952-Aug. 18, 1952.
    - Pan American Airways, Inc., 1952-1953 (Box 101, Folder 26)
      Aug. 19, 1952-April 1953.
    - Pan American Airways, Inc., 1953-1959 (Box 101, Folder 27)
      May 1953-Sept. 1959.
    - Pan American Airways, Inc.-Guided Missile Base, 1957-1958 (Box 101, Folder 28)
      1957-Feb. 1958.
    - Pan American Airways, Inc., 1952 (Box 101, Folder 29)
      June 12, 1952-July 18, 1952.
    - Pan American Airways, Inc., 1952 (Box 101, Folder 30)
      Jan. 1952-June 11, 1952.
    - Pan American Airways, Inc., 1948-1951 (Box 101, Folder 31)
    - Pan American Airways, Inc., 1947 (Box 102, Folder 1)
      Feb. 1947-Dec. 1947.
    - Pan American Airways, Inc., 1946-1947 (Box 102, Folder 2)
      April 1946-Jan. 1947.
    - Pan American Airways, Inc., 1944-1946 (Box 102, Folder 3)
      Oct. 1944-March 1946.
    - Pan American Airways, Inc., 1945-1948 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Pan American Airways, Inc., 1945-1948 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Pan American Airways, Inc., 1946-1949 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Pan American Airways, Inc., 1947-1949 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Pan American Airways, Inc., 1944-1946 (Box 102, Folder 8)
      Dec. 1944-46.
    - Pan American Airways, Inc., 1945-1946 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Pan American Airways, Inc., 1944-1945 (Box 102, Folder 10)
      Oct. 1944-April 1945.
    - Pan American Airways, Inc., 1945 (Box 102, Folder 11)
      May 1945-Dec. 1945.
  - Sub-Series 230-417. Organization
    - Joint Interchange Bureau-Pueblo, Colorado, 1928-1945 (Box 102, Folder 12)
  - Sub-Series 230-419. Organization
    - Oakland Terminal Railway, 1953 (Box 102, Folder 13)
  - Sub-Series 230-420. Organization
    - Wharton & Northern Railroad Company, 1942 (Box 100, Folder 24)
      1942 May 6
    - Northeast Airlines, Inc., 1944-1947 (Box 102, Folder 14)
      1944-Jan. 1947.
  - Sub-Series 230-421. Organization
    - Sand Springs Railway, 1937-1945 (Box 102, Folder 15)
  - Sub-Series 230-425. Organization
    - Niagara, St. Catherines & Toronto Railway, 1944-1945 (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - Sub-Series 230-428. Organization
    - Canadian Interior Navigation & Stevedoring Companies, 1942-1950 (Box 103, Folder 3)
  - Sub-Series 230-430. Organization
    - Yermo Freight Handlers, Inc., 1942 (Box 100, Folder 28)
  - Sub-Series 230-432. Organization
    - Trans-Atlantic Shipping Companies, 1946 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Sub-Series 230-436. Organization
    - Air Transport Industry, 1961-1963 (Box 103, Folder 5)
      Jan. 1, 1961-Dec. 31, 1963.